brownstoner.com 2013-10-18

# Privacy Policy | Brownstoner

Your privacy is important to us at Newburgh Restoration Media (“Newburgh Restoration Media”, “we”, or “our”). Accordingly, we have established and implemented information handling practices for www.newburghrestoration.com (the “Site”) that we believe are consistent with the highest standards and best practices of organizations doing business on the Internet. This Privacy Policy describes the practices that apply to the Site, including, specifically, the information we collect about you, when and how we collect that information and what may happen to that information. We have prepared this detailed Privacy Policy because we believe you should know as much as possible about our practices so that you can make informed decisions about how you use the Site. Capitalized terms in this Privacy Policy have the meaning ascribed to them in the Terms of Use <http://www.newburghrestoration.com/terms-of-use/>.

**When You Visit The Site**

You can always visit the Site without revealing who you are or providing any personal information. When you visit the Site we do collect usage information, but it is anonymous and is not linked to you as an individual. We may use this data to better understand, for example, how the Site is navigated, how many visitors arrive at specific pages, the length and frequency of stays at the Site, the types of browsers and computer operating systems used by our visitors and the Internet Protocol addresses from which our visitors connect to the Site. We may use this information to improve the Site’s Content and ease of use.

**When You Become a User**

When you sign up as a User, you provide us with information such as your name, email address, zip code and other contact information. We may use the information you provide on or through the Site to improve the Site’s Content and ease of use, or as you otherwise consent in advance. We will take all reasonable efforts to protect this information, and we will not share it with third parties such as direct marketers without your request or consent. However, _you acknowledge and agree that we may provide your personal information (a) to third-party providers of services to the Site, such as computer programmers and technicians, provided that they are under obligation to us to protect this information, and (b) to other third parties when compelled by a court order or other legal process._

**Security**

The Site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We safeguard the security of the data you send us with physical, electronic, and other procedures. However, it is not possible to guarantee the security or integrity of information disclosed online. Because no data transmission over the Internet is completely secure, we urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet, including when you are using the Site.

**When You Post Content**

Users may post or upload User Content to the Site. As between Newburgh Restoration Media and you and between other Users and you, you are the owner of all User Content that you upload, email or post to or within the Site. You grant us permission to use all such User Content on and in connection with the Site. For more information, see the Terms of Use <http://www.newburghrestoration.com/terms-of-use/> for the Site. When You Submit Feedback to Us In order to submit comments or questions to the site, you will have to register for a user account, a process that involves, among other disclosures, the provision of your email address. We will not disclose your email address or other personal information to third parties, except as expressly set forth in this Privacy Policy. We may contact you via the email address you provide to answer your question(s), clarify the information you have submitted and send you emails, from time to time, as part of our Email List. (For additional information, see the Email List section of the Terms of Use <http://www.newburghrestoration.com/terms-of-use/>.)

**Cookies and Pixel Tags**

We, or a third-party advertiser acting on our behalf, may place a “cookie” or “pixel tag” on your personal computer when you come to the Site or visit a site on which we advertise. These devices are small computer files that our computer sends to your computer and that your computer sends back to us each time you visit the Site. We may use these devices to collect data to help us personalize and improve your experiences on the Site. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. However, you can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the sites you visit. If you decide not to accept our cookies, your ability to use some features on the Site may be impaired.

**Third-Party Advertisers**

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [networkadvertising.org](http://networkadvertising.org/).

**Links to Third-Party Websites**

The Site may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave the Site and to read the privacy statements of every website that collects personally identifiable information. Our Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by the Site and does not cover information collected elsewhere.

**California Privacy Rights**

Pursuant to California Civil Code § 1798.83, a California resident who has provided personal information to a business with which he/she has established a business relationship has the right to request from that business information about whether the business has disclosed personal information to any third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. In general, if the business has made such a disclosure of personal information, the business is required to provide a list of all third parties to whom such personal information was disclosed in the preceding calendar year, as well as a list of the categories of personal information that were disclosed, upon receipt of a request by a California resident. However, under the law, a business is not required to provide the above-described lists if the business adopts and discloses to the public (in its privacy policy) a policy of not disclosing personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless the customer first affirmatively agrees to the disclosure, as long as the business maintains and discloses this policy. Rather, the business may comply with the law by notifying the customer of his or her right to prevent disclosure of personal information and providing a cost free means to exercise that right. As noted above, we do not disclose such personal information to third parties for direct marketing purposes unless you affirmatively agree to such disclosure.

**Modifications to this Privacy Policy**

Newburgh Restoration Media reserves the right to change the terms, conditions, and notices in this Privacy Policy at any time for any reason. If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [newburghrestoration@gmail.com](mailto:newburghrestoration@gmail.com).

Last updated as of July 19, 2013.
